

# ANGELA GUMBS

Website Designer Web Project Manager

Personal Information

Phone:

+44 734 103 0540

Email:

angela.n.gumbs@gmail.com

Website:

www.angelagumbs.com

LinkedIn:

Angela Gumbs

Soft Skills

Creative Thinking

Adaptive | Problem Solving

**Detail Oriented** 

Communication

### **PROFILE**

A passionate Web Designer and Project Manager with over 15 years of experience. I have managed website design from concept to final product launch, working directly with clients to establish project scope, interaction guidelines, and project time lines. Worked on over 90 projects in several industries including finance, tourism and local government. Managed, maintained and updated existing websites for customers and provide customer service. I am Self-motivated and adaptable with great research and analytical skills

## **WORK HISTORY**

**2017 – 2018** Amsterdam Say..webdev

Web Project Manager

Worked on contract based website projects, providing consultations, design concepts, WordPress customization, basic SEO services and social media implementation. Set up websites hosting, purchasing domain and working within plesk and cpanel to manage and maintain web projects.

**2005 – 2017** St. Kitts eCaribbean Limited

Chief Creative Developer

Successfully managed projects from graphic design conception to website launch working individual and with a team. Maintained active communication with clients to ensure project goals are met.

Designed and customized WordPress based website, implementing plugins for SEO and Social Media efficiency. Ensured smooth responsiveness for mobile compatibility.

Prospected and negotiated website revamps for existing and new clients to improve efficiency and appeal with an aim to increase website traffic.

**2003 – 2005** St. Kitts

Net.kn

**Website Designer** 

Created graphic website layout and developed customized websites and CMS for local and regional businesses, using HTML, CSS and classic ASP. Built and integrated custom database.



## Hobbies & Interests

Languages

Latin Dance

Mindfulness Meditation

Movies

Walking

Growth Reading

## **EDUCATION**

## Web Development Professional

CIW Web Development Professional Certification

## **Business Management**

Clarence Fitzroy Bryant College Cambridge Advanced Level certification

### Accounting

Clarence Fitzroy Bryant College Cambridge Advanced Level Certification

## **ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES**

With a growing interest is digital marketing, I am currently taking online curses to enhance my knowledge and skills set in advanced SEO services, content development and marketing, Email marketing and inbound marketing.